http://www.daffodilday.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Statement
Your Personal Information is being or has been collected by the Cancer Council to facilitate services or products requested by you and/or to keep you informed about Cancer Council related activities.  We may send you information about programs, products, services, fundraising or other activities which we think may interest you.  Your Personal Information may be provided to third parties where required by law or so that such third parties may provide Cancer Council with services.  In so doing your Personal Information may be disclosed to overseas recipients.  Please refer to our Privacy Policy (which is available on the relevant Cancer Council website as listed at the link below or on request by calling 1300 65 65 85) for further details. By providing your information to us you consent to your information being disclosed or used for this purpose.  We will take reasonable steps to ensure that such third parties deal with your information appropriately and only for Cancer Council purposes.  Please refer to our Privacy Policy, or details in the relevant communication, if you wish to unsubscribe.  Our Privacy Policy also explains how you can contact us to access and correct your personal information or make a privacy complaint.
“Cancer Council”, “we”, “us” or “our” means Cancer Council Australia or the Cancer Council in the State or Territory in which you are participating in the fundraising activity, or in your State or Territory of residence (as applicable).  Full details of Cancer Council Australia and its State and Territory members are available here
Cancer Council is registered with the Australian Taxation Office as an Income tax Exempt Charity. All donations over $2 are tax deductible.
Privacy Policy  |  Disclaimer  |  Contact Us
